Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Records WAG 006
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Counsel Files, 1940-1975
  - Department Stores Service Co, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Dial Fabrics, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Diamond Quilting Co, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Diamond Yarn Co, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Direct Mail, Labor Board Cases, 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Direct Mail, Master Contract Assoc, 1966-1968 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Distributive Realty Corp, 1952-1964 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Donnelly Blanthorn Corp, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Doral Fabrics, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Doubleday & Co (S. Bopko Arb), 1967-1969 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Downtown Dry Goods Jobbers Assoc, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Dubin Lace & Trimming Corp, 1963-1964 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Durable Paint Co, 1967, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Durex Hardware Mfg, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Dykeman Loeb & Co, 1965-1967 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Dynamic Offset, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - E.J. Creeden, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Eagle Stationers & Printers, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Eagle Window Display Advertising Co, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Eastern Fabrics Corp, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Eckhouse Shoe Co, 1969-1972 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Economic Stabilization, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Edwin Rudell, 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Efrain Velasquez et al vs Commarato Local 400, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Eichman Fabrics, 1963-1965 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Einson-Freeman Co, 1947-1964 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Eugene Eisner (Personal), 1964-1969 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Electro Film Offset Printing Co & Lewis Illustrated Offset Corp, 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 24-25)
  - Elite Letter Co, 1956-1966 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Em-Bar Industries, 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Empire Corrugated Container Corp, 1963-1970 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Empire Textile Corp, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Employment Act Suit, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Employment Act Suit, 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
  - Engler Mill Work, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Ezra Cohen, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Europe Craft Imports, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - FFK Sales Corp, 1962-1964 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - F. W. Woolworth, 1965-1974 (Box 36, Folder 8-9)
  - Fabrics by Rembrandt, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Fabricworld Textile, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Fairway Plastics Inc, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Famous Wool Corp, 1965-1969 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Fifth Ave Letter & Litho, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Fireside Farics, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Fischl Brass Button, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Flint Copas Metal Stamping Co, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Frankel Associates, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Franklin Textile, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    NOT IN FOLDERS--1975-1976; Franklin Textile (17 volumes of arbitration case files).
  - Funding Systems Leasing Corp, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Furlager Manufacturing Co., 1952 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Garber Hardware, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Gaylord Container, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Gem Albums, 1962-1971 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - General Merchandise Corp, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Girl Craft Industries, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Glad Hatter, 1965, 1968-1971 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Glemby, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 10-15)
  - Golden Eagle Mutual Life Insurance, 1967-1972 (Box 37, Folder 16-17)
  - Goldenbro Textiles, 1966-1969 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Goldfarb Bros., 1970 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Max Goldfrank, 1952-1954 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Sol Goldwasser, 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Andrew Goodall, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Goodwin's Inc, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Gray & Gray Textile Co, 1966-1971 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Griffel Textiles, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Grossman Bros, 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Grossmark Textiles, 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - H&S Oil, 1934, 1962-1965 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - H. Greenwald, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 1-7)
  - H. Jelinek Dental Alloys, 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - H. J. Stotter Inc, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - H. L. Gross, 1949, 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Hackett, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Harold Armstrong, 1965-1967 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Harry S. Horowitz, 1962, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Hartz Mountain, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 14-21)
  - ENTIRE BOX -- 1974 -- Hartz Mountain, undated (Box 39)
  - Hawthorne Books Inc, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Jack Hazelkorn, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Hecht & Biern Knitwear, 1961-1968 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Helen Neushaeffer, 1955-1971 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Heinsheimer Bros, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Hertz Drivurself Stations Inc, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Hollander Lace & Embroidery, 1962-1965 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Holly Stores, 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - The Hopp Press, 1965-1965 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Hotopp Paint & Varnish, 1968, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Howard Johnson, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Hughes Direct Mail Service, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Imperial Textile Co, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Independent Quilting, 1959-1967 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Interstate Knitting Mills, 1948-1951 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Intrastate Bag Co, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Ipco Hospital Supply, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Irval Sales Co., 1966 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Irving Borten, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Irving Vinitz DBA Baby Specialties, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Isodor Kaplan, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Izbel Products, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - J. Homestock, 1972-1974 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - J. Levine Textile, 1968-1974 (Box 40, Folder 24-25)
  - J. J. Berliner, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - J. J. Edelson, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Jacques Maisch Ltd, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - James Rubin D/B/A Orthodontic Service, 1964-1969 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Jem Refolding, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Jeno Guttman, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Jo-Ed Bundlers, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - John Hancock Mutual Life, 1965-1968 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - John Wiley & Sons, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 34-38)
  - Jonas Shoppes, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Joseph Taffet--Artistic Silk Hosiery, 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - ENTIRE BOX --1970-1974 -- Joyce Sportswear, undated (Box 41)
  - Joyce Sportswear, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Kandahar Sportswear, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Kane Steel Co/ Kane Mfg, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Kannen Bowling Center, 1965-1967 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Kay Green Corp, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Kaytee Imports, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - R. M. Kaufman, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 7-9)
  - Keller Tickets, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Kimko Auto Products, 1969-1971 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Kirby Mills, 1966-1968 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Kitty Kelly Shoe Co, 1951-1951 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Saul Klein, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Knopf Instruments, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Koppers Company, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Koret Fabrics, 1960-1964 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - L. Commarato vs Art Steel, 1971-1973 (Box 42, Folder 18-23)
  - L. Luria, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Long News, 1962-1964 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Laufer & Rothbaum, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Laura Modes, 1962-1964 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Leather Coating Company, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Laura Lebron, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Ledding Sales Co, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Lehigh Corrugated Container Corp, 1949, 1951-1952 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Leo Racoff Jewelers, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Lerner Shops, 1946-1948 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Lerner Shops, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - The Letter Shop, 1963-1966 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Lewis Products, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Lidz Bros, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln Button & Thread, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Little Fawn Co, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Lloyd A Fry Roofing, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Local 59 FTA V FTA CIO, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Local 115 DPO FTA, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Local 810 Libel, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - London Records, 1966-1968 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Loren Service, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Louis Weinberg Associates, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Luminall Paints, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Lupar Enterprises, 1966-1969 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Lyle Stuart, 1948-1973 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - M. W. Parsons--Plymouth (S.B. Penick), 1959-1964 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Mac Levy Associates, 1958-1967 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Madison Square Offset, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Makel Textiles, 1965-1967 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Maradel Products, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Marriello Fabrics, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Leslie Martin, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Mastercraft Lithographers, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Master Touch Dental Labs, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - May Parros, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Maytag & Label Corp, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 34-36)
  - Medo Photo Supply, 1966-1968 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Melburt Products Cooperative, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Melcher & Landau {Remainder of box is 5 volumes from Melcher & Landau case, not in folders.}, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 3-7)
  - Melcher & Landua--2 volumes, not in folders, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - Meldisco Warehouse, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Midtown Manufacturing, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Miles Shoe (Melville Shoe), 1968-1970 (Box 45, Folder 6-11)
  - Miller v. Abreu (Security Plan), 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Milton C. Johnson, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Minimum Wages (Industrial Commissioner), 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Mitchell Mogal, 1964-1965 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Mode Fabric, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Monarch Warehouse, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Monroe Sander Corp, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 18-19)
  - Monroe Sander Corp, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - Monthly Publication of the ACLU, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Mt Vernon Prosthetics, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Mucon Corp/ Republic Electronic, 1964-1965 (Box 46, Folder 5-6)
  - Muray Textile, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - NAWCAS (National Association of Women & Children's Apparel Salesesmen) - Includes files on individual companies, legal developments, business trends, Canada, 1958, 1963-1975 (Box 46, Folder 8-21)
  - Najac Textile, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - National Birth Record Co., 1964 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - National Business Lists, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - National Letter Service, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Nat Nattman, 1960, 1972-1974 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Nelda Sportswear, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - New England Textile Co, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - New Jersey Fireworks, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - New York Central Bookbinding, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - New York Merchandise, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - New York Shoe Trading, 1961-1966 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - New York Telephone, 1967-1971 (Box 47, Folder 4-5)
  - New York University, 1970-1971 (Box 47, Folder 6-12)
  - New York University, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 1-5)
  - District 65 v Nixon et al, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Norman Plastic Co, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Nu-Way Shoe Co, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Oken Fabrics, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Old Dutch Mustard, 1965, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Olympic Glove Co, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Orthodontists Service, 1965-1966 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Overland Fabrics Ltd, 1965, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Owen Illinois Glass Co, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - P.S. Creations Inc, 1966-1969 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Pacesetter Industries, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Victor A. Pagan, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Page Studio, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Paige Hat Co, 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Palm Shore Dry Goods Co (Gerald Shorofsky), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Palmar Millinery, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Palmer Hardware, 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Paramount Surgical Supply, 1968-1972 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Paul Cohen Merchandise, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Penthouse Manufacturing, 1964-1968 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Petitions Filed by Union and Employer during strike period, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Pickram Hats, 1966-1969 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Plasticloth Products, 1967-1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1970-1972 (Box 49, Folder 2-12)
  - Pratt Paper Products, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Prentiss Lane Inc, 1965-1968 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Presstype, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Public Service Letter & Printing Co, 1964-1967 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Pulitzer Tiremakers, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Qual-Fab, 1965-1966 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - R.D. Cortina, 1966-1971 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - R.O. Kent, 1951 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - R & M Kaufmann (NAWCAS), 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 21-24)
  - R & M Kaufmann (NAWCAS), 1971-1973 (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
  - RWDSU disaffiliation--Civil rights, pension disputes, minutes, legal exhibits, 1944-1970 (Box 50, Folder 4-20)
  - RWDSU pension dispute (Livingston deposition), 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Armando Ramirez (FTA), 1951 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Raxon Fabrics, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Jesse Ray, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Raymar Textile Mills, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Rego Letter Service, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Reliable Buyers--Meyer Dreiblatt, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Remy Sportswear & Shetland Knitting Mills, 1961-1962 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Republic Container, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Revlon Inc, 1970-1973 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Reyes v Art Steel, 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Ritchie & Page Dish, 1956-1966 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Rite Service Warehouse, 1947, 1969-1970 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Louis Rivera, 1970-1972 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Rodless Decorations, 1966-1967 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Ronald Cappucio, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Ronson Service, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Rosen & Pollack, 1963-1965 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Rosenbluth Bros, 1964-1966 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Roseanna Knitwear, 1965-1970 (Box 51, Folder 20-23)
  - Rothchild Bros Textile, 1962, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Royal London Co, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Royal Synthetics, 1965, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Margaret Ryan Estate, 1963-1964 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - S. Klein (Aloha Pailet), 1950 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Sage Fabrics, 1969-1971 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Sam Biern, 1947-1952 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Samuel Cohen DBA (Charles S. Cohen), 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Samuel Miller, 1967-1968 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Saul S. Neagreann & Cravatex, 1964-1965 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Security Plan Arbitrations, 1966-1969 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Severance Pay Fund, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Shel-Gold Fabrics, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - ShieldAlloy Corp, 1964-1969 (Box 52, Folder 1-4)
  - Sidney Davis Co, 1964-1967 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Solar Curtain, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Stamp & Album Co of America, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Standard Sample Card, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Standard Scientific Supply Co, 1965, ca.1971-1972 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Starward Fabrics, 1970-1973 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Strand Bookstore (not in folders), 1970-1973 (Box 52, Folder 11-17)
  - Streim Fabrics Inc, 1968-1971 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Supak & Sons, 1971-1973 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Supreme Farics, 1959-1961 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Symbol Press, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - T. Mark Furniture Co, 1967-1968 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Teachers College Employee Association, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Teachers College Employee Association, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Traffic Union, 1962-1971 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Temple University, 1969-1972 (Box 53, Folder 3-6)
  - Thomas Burke, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Thomas Pride Mills, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Thomson Leeds Co, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Tifford Furniture & Appliance, 1965-1978 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Tonel Fabrics, 1961-1970 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Torrence v Lebold, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Tri-Chem Inc, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - University of Chicago, 1967-1972 (Box 53, Folder 14-20)
  - ENTIRE BOX -- University of Chicago, 1969-1974 (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_ab4ea0ab4df0d3c6eee7c2458c7dbe6c)
  - V.P. Adams, 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Varsity Drive-In Restaurants, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Village Voice, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Wade Laundry & Dry Cleaning, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Wage & Price Controls, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Wage Stabilization, 1951-1952 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Warner Bros, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Wayne Steel Co, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Weider Distributors, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Wel-Bilt Display, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
  - Wm Teres Co, 1965-1968 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - WIPO, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 13-14)
  - Wisefield's Inc, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Working Poor Exemption, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Yale University, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 17-18)
  - Miscellaneous, 1964-1968 (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
  - Weidman Fabrics, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Unfair Labor Practice Charges & Petitions, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous arbitrations, 1965-1968 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962-1969 (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
  - Miscellaneous Unfair Labor Practice Charges (union & employer), 1965-1969 (Box 56, Folder 9-10)
  - Miscellaneous arbitration, 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Series III: Finance Department, 1940-1964
  - Finance Department weekly reports, 1940-1948 (Box 57, Folder 1-8)
  - Finance Department weekly reports, 1951 (Box 57, Folder 9-10)
  - Finance Department weekly reports, 1955-1956 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Finance Department monthly reports, 1940-1948 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
  - Finance Department monthly reports, 1951-1970 (Box 58, Folder 4-9)
  - Finance Department yearly reports, 1942-1961 (Box 58, Folder 10-13)
  - Finance Department membership inventories, 1941-1950 (Box 58, Folder 14-18)
  - Finance Department membership inventories, 1953-1964 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Series IV: Affiliates, 1937-1950
  - Subseries IV:A: Local 5 (Stern), 1939-1950
    - Assessments, 1947-1948 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Attendance Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Beauty Salon (Sophia Co), 1942-1949 (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
    - Beauty Salon, negotiations, 1947-1948 (Box 59, Folder 5-6)
    - Constitution Committee, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, general, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, management/Sophia Co, 1940-1950 (Box 59, Folder 9-11)
    - Correspondence, membership, 1949-1950 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Division, commission, 1946-1949 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Division, office, 1945-1946 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Division, warehouse, 1947-1948 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Division, workrooms, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Elections, 1943-1944 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Election, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Expelled & suspended members, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Shop grievances, 1947-1948 (Box 59, Folder 20-22)
    - Adjusted grievances, 1948-1949 (Box 59, Folder 23-28)
    - Grievances, Beauty Salon, 1944-1949 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
    - Grievances, Management, 1947-1949 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Grievances, Reported & Discussed, 1947-1949 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Grievances & Shop matters, 1943-1947 (Box 60, Folder 5-9)
    - Layoffs, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Meetings, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Meetings, 1948-1949 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Organizers Reports to Executive Board & Membership Meetings, 1943-1947 (Box 60, Folder 14-16)
    - Negotiations, Sterns, 1946-1949 (Box 60, Folder 17-19)
    - Negotiations, demands, Beauty Salon, 1944 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Newly Employed Lists, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Operational Expenses, 1939-1947 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Program, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 23-24)
    - THURSDAYS TILL NINE (script of a play)***, undated (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - War Labor Board, petitions & approval, 1943-1945 (Box 60, Folder 26-28)
  - Subseries IV:B: Local 121 (Gas, Coke, Chemical), 1937-1950
    - Applicator Brush, 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Arnesto Paint, 1947-1950 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Art-Tex Adhesive, 1945-1950 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Adelphi Paint, 1944-1948 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Alco Manufacturing, 1946-1947 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Anigraphic Process, 1944-1947 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Varnish Manufacturing, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Buckingham Wax, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Caldwell Products, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Camel Lead & Color, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Colonial Works, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Commonwealth Color, 1945-1947 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - D'Orsay Sales, 1947-1950 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Debevoise Paint, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Empire Findings, 1945 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Endo Products, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Estro Chemical, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Gesell Inc, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Glyco Products, 1944-1948 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Industrial Latex, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Jewel Sheen, 1945-1948 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Korex Coating Corp, 1946-1949 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Hema Chemical, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Linde Air Local 317, 1937-1949 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Lithaloys, 1944-1947 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - NY Quinine & Chemical, 1941-1948 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Polak's Frutal Works, 1944-1948 (Box 61, Folder 27-31)
    - Presto Plastics, 1946-1950 (Box 61, Folder 32-36)
    - Rubber Corporation of America, 1944-1950 (Box 61, Folder 37-41)
    - Paragon Paint & Varnish, 1946-1948 (Box 61, Folder 42-44)
    - Red Star Chemical, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 45)
    - Saponina Chemical, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 46)
    - United Backing, 1950 (Box 61, Folder 47)
    - Vico (Van Inderstine) (Folder #2 is all leaflets, 1944-1947 (Box 61, Folder 48-49)
    - Werner Plastics, 1945-1946 (Box 61, Folder 50)
    - W.D. Printing Ink, 1946-1948 (Box 61, Folder 51-54)
    - Zophar Mills, 1946-1948 (Box 61, Folder 55-56)
  - Subseries IV:C: Drug Trade Salesmen's Union, 1937-1950
    - DTSU, General, 1943-1948 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - DTSU, Contracts, 1945-1948 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - NLRB Decisions, 1944-1947 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Unorganized shops, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Abbott Laboratories, 1945-1946 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - American Drug Syndicate, 1940-1948 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - American Drug Syndicate, Barnie Mishkin File, 1946-1948 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - American Drug Syndicate, Contracts, 1946-1949 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - American Pharmaceutical, 1946 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Applicator Brush, 1946-1950 (Box 62, Folder 10-12)
    - Andrew Jergens, 1944-1946 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Ayerst, McKenna & Harrison, 1944-1947 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - B.S. Colnes, 1944-1945 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - D. Kaltman, 1946-1948 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - E.J. Barry, 1945-1946 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Frederick Stearns, 1946-1947 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Frederick Stearns, Atlantic Division, 1943-1945 (Box 62, Folder 19-20)
    - Hoffman LaRoche, 1944-1948 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - InterCity Drug, 1946-1947 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - IVC--International Vitamin--Ives Cameron, 1946-1949 (Box 62, Folder 23-25)
    - John T. Stanley, 1943 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - Lehn & Fink Products, 1945-1946 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - McKesson & Robbins, 1937-1946 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Mutual Drug, undated (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - Norwich Pharmacal Co, 1943-1946 (Box 62, Folder 30-31)
    - Norwich Pharmacal Co, 1944-1948 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)